Peter Onisha Peregbakumo

Nigeria



linkedin.com/in/peter-onishaperegbakumo-526a34152



perezpeter32@gmail.com

Summary

I am experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web and mobile applications - having an in-depth knowledge in Flutter & Dart and also including advanced HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and Laravel. Strong background in management, leadership and familiar with design tools such as Figma, Adobe XD, and Photoshop.

Experience



EpayGh

Sep 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months +)



Ҳ Software Developer

AgroCenta (Holdings) Limited

Jun 2018 - Jul 2019 (1 year 2 months)

UI Design, UI implementation, Web application Development and cross-platform development.



Photography and Videography Intern

Lancaster University Ghana

Nov 2017 - Aug 2018 (10 months)

Photoshoot for online and printing campaigns, Event coverage, Video commercial productions for social media.



■ Web Developer Internship

ibrand Africa

Jul 2017 - Sep 2017 (3 months)

Develop websites for clients (Both Frontend and Backend)



Remote Web Developer Intern

Hotels.ng

Apr 2017 - Jul 2017 (4 months)

Mockup Designs, Implement UI designs, worked on APIs, Co-developed external projects.

Education



Lancaster University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2015 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications



Google Certified Android Developer - Udacity



Certified Flutter Developer - The App Brewery

cert_36phvx6c

Honors & Awards

The Founders' Award - Transnational Academic Group

The Founders' Award was established by the Co-Founders of Transnational Academic Group (TAG), Mr Zafar Siddiqi and MR Rakesh Wahi to recognize the student who best embodies the values of TAG, and has demonstrated this throughout their time at the University.

The values of TAG Ghana can be encapsulated in the acronym LIACC, translating into: Loyalty, Integrity, Attitude, Competence and Commitment.



Lancaster Role Model Award - Lancaster University

Oct 2017



Provost List Awards - Lancaster University

Oct 2016

The Lancaster Provost List Award is a way to honor students with distinctions at the end of the academic

To qualify for the award, one has to have three (3) E's (Excellent) or two (2) V's (Very good) and an E (Excellent).

Skills

Web Development • Android Development • Project Management • User Interface Design • Software Development • Flutter Developement • Mobile Developement